Good to see you, my lord.
How's it going?
It feels good to be back in front of the computer.
In front of the keyboard and the mouse and my controllers and my dollars.
Oh yeah.
How are you?
I'm great, thank you for asking.
I had a lovely week.
I was out touching grass.
I was talking to people.
You know, I was just hanging out with my cat.
I watched some movies.
It was good.
It was nice.
But now I'm craving the games again.
Time to bring the games back.
Infinite games.
Unlimited games.
I know, grass is oo, because my allergies are kind of crazy with that.
But, good news on that.
I think I may have found some medicine that works!
So I took some new medicine at the start of this week as well.
Or last week, I should say.
And, I've had very minimal allergies.
So it was even better being outside.
Yeah.
Finally.
It could just be a coincidence that, you know, the pollen was low or whatever.
But I checked the, uh, the forecast.
And it did say, hi, Poland.
So I don't know.
Weird.
How are you guys doing?
I yearned for- exactly, I yearned for the games.
What's the plan today?
There is no plan today.
We're going off script today.
Today we're playing Isaac, and we're not gonna have a plan.
Because I don't even remember what I did last time.
Oh, by the way, guys, if you haven't seen the announcement.
Minecraft on July 17th.
It's coming.
Yeah, no script today.
No script.
Yeah, I know.
It's- it's- it is what it is.
Sometimes, you know, budget- budget cards, uh...
No script.
I've been getting that Minecraft itch again.
In fact, I've had the itch for a bit.
And I actually did plan the 17th a while ago.
But, uh, yeah.
It is with mods.
I don't know which mods yet, though.
We're gonna have to figure that out.
Or I will have to figure that out.
It could be whatever.
Maybe create.
Maybe something else.
I don't know.
I haven't yet decided on that.
Most likely create, I guess.
But yeah.
It's gonna be exciting.
It's gonna be good to play some Minecraft again.
Cause I watched some, uh...
I don't know if you know the streamer.
Oh man, what's his name?
Why can't I remember this now?
Sariyu.
He's like a World of Warcraft streamer mainly.
That's how I know him.
He started playing Minecraft blind, actually.
Maybe like 10 days ago or so.
And I've been watching some of those episodes on YouTube.
And it's actually amazing to watch.
I can recommend that, guys.
If you're looking for some more stuff like that.
So I was like, damn.
You know?
That also got me back into it a little bit more.
Like, that got me hyped.
Yeah, yeah.
How you spell the name?
Uh, I'm gonna write it in chat.
He's quite a bit popular streamer though.
Usually he streams World of Warcraft.
That's like his main game, right?
But, yeah.
Check it out.
He's such a cool dude as well.
I love him.
Alright, guys.
It's time for some Binding of Isaac.
Let's see if I can even play this game.
Or if I have forgotten everything.
Oh, it's been a while.
Zoop.
I think last time I did a bunch of challenges, actually.
Now that I think about it.
Let me see here.
The family man...
The nose?
The hose?
The host?
Purist?
And now we get to the red ones.
Not today though.
Or maybe today.
But I wanna do something else first.
How about we play some Isaac to get back into Isaac?
Huh?
Because look at all the achievements we have on Isaac.
That's right.
We don't have any achievements on Isaac.
So we gotta get some.
We have killed the heart.
We have gotten a page, which I think is...
I think that one is the beast, actually.
Because the page, you know, with the note or whatever.
From dad.
So yeah, I think that was the beast.
We gotta do all kinds of other things though.
So, let's go!
Win streak of minus one.
I don't think that counter has ever been higher than two.
Which is insane.
By the way, uh, quick check guys.
Is the music too loud right now?
Because I may have fucked up some settings since last time.
Is it what it usually is?
Or...
Is it different?
I'm gonna check chat.
Hold on.
Uh...
It's chill.
It sounds like always.
Someone's saying yes.
I can turn down just a tad though.
So...
Perhaps a bit high.
Okay.
Oh wait, let me do...
Actually, can I...
I'm just gonna do it in game.
If I can.
Options...
Is that too low?
Is that way too low?
Because it could be too low, I guess.
I can turn up a little bit in OBS here.
We find a middle ground.
Actually, no, no, actually, I need to...
I need to have it a little higher.
For me, it's not very loud.
It's better like this for me.
So I'm gonna turn it down for you guys.
Uh...
Like that.
Okay, this should probably be fine.
Let's do this.
Okay, so that's how you shoot.
Oh, by the way, I think I also forgot to turn up the SFX again.
There we go.
Alright, we can go step maybe.
If I want to.
Do I want to?
Let me consider.
No.
Not yet.
Only if I find a bunch of hearts.
That's the rule.
We got a Tinted Rock already.
And we have a bomb!
Ah, but...
Actually, wait, wait, wait.
I'm not gonna destroy this Tinted Rock yet.
I have a reason for it, okay?
For example, I wanna...
If it drops a blue heart, I wanna save that for later.
So if I wanna go into the curse room, I'm gonna wait.
I couldn't really get that sentence out in a way that makes sense, but I hope you understood what I meant.
I'm gonna keep my options open.
Yoi!
Wow!
I still got the skills.
Dude, this is a crazy room.
Wait, is the music different?
That guitar riff?
I don't remember that.
Okay, maybe it is actually not new.
Okay, I guess I do this first.
Oops.
What is that?
A, uh...
Brontosaurus.
Don't get near me.
Varicose veins.
Launches a ring of ten large tears each time I take damage.
Mmm.
Why not?
Very underwhelming, honestly, but, you know...
Ooh, that's a cheap PhD!
Yo!
I could blow up the machine!
I am very tempted to do that.
Very tempted.
But let's wait.
That was masterfully done.
If I do say so myself.
And I do say so myself.
Hey, come here.
Can we get perfection, maybe?
Come on, money!
Damn.
Oh!
That's a lot of flies.
Like, isn't that way more than usual?
Imagine having a Azazel right now.
That would be so much better.
But you could say that at any point in the game, right?
Oh, we're gonna play a Azazel today as well.
Or maybe the modified Azazel.
The new Azazel.
The nays Azazel.
Massazel.
So I have two bombs, which means we can blow up the machine and do the tinted.
Uh, boss first.
Monstro!
This guy's kinda dangerous actually.
Oh god!
Okay, we're fine.
He has a lot of HP.
Are you gonna jump on me?
Wow!
Stop puking!
Oh, here we go.
Dude, so far I'm killing it.
Beautiful!
Perfection.
Experimental treatment.
Yes.
Nice!
We got an extra heart!
More damage!
Less range though.
But all in all...
Mwah!
Beautiful.
Absolutely wonderful.
Did I leave hearts behind?
I don't think so.
Let's go blow up some shit.
Yeah!
Definitely blowing up some machine.
Boink!
I could've potentially hit this guy as well at the same time.
But...
I didn't wanna risk it.
Spawns a puddle of slowing black creep.
Okay.
Now we go back for...
The tinted rock.
Because watch, it's gonna have a blue heart in it.
Which means we're gonna be ready for the next stage.
Aww.
So hard!
Fuck yeah!
I'm gonna say no to the curse room.
Actually, I probably should've went into the curse room before I picked that up.
Ah.
One mistake made so far.
That's acceptable.
It's fine.
Cheers guys.
I've got ice tea today.
Because it's so hot outside.
And it's filled up to the brim with ice.
I bought a huge bag of ice.
I'm gonna have ice for a long time.
No!
That was very poorly played.
Good thing we had a buffer.
Also, we're going angels, of course.
Wait!
I forgot I had a d6!
I have to remember that.
I could've potentially re-rolled the, uh...
Oh shit.
No, no, no, no!
Don't take my...
Energy!
Ah!
Asshole!
Oh, it didn't empty my entire energy.
It was just one bar.
Oh, in that case, that's no problem.
Just ring around the Rosie with these guys.
It's...
It's fine.
Oh man, oh man, oh man!
No!
Okay, buffer gone, guys.
It went too well anyway.
How does this happen?
I completely forgot how far they jump.
Okay, let's go north.
Mmm...
No bombs.
It was so good until it wasn't, you know?
Okay, let's see what we get here.
We can re-roll it, worst case.
I'm gonna destroy your poop!
Do they know?
Sweet!
Come on!
Can- I mean...
I don't wanna re-roll this!
This is good!
Also, hey, we- we got the demon!
So...
Hmm, wait, should I go demon?
Guys!
I'm going demon!
I have decided.
We're going demon mode.
Blood rights...
Uh...
Wait, hold on.
Let me destroy these first.
I'm gonna re-roll these for sure though.
Cause I don't like both of these.
Okay, now I can think.
Uh... yeah.
Reroll for sure.
Death's list.
Ah!
I'm not too happy about this either.
Dead cat is...
The problem with dead cat...
Is that it's gonna reduce...
All my HP to one.
Right?
And that's bad.
Cause I have four right now, and I like having four.
But I guess it's kinda free in that case.
If you only had two HP.
Wait, how would that work?
I wonder.
Anyway.
Death's list.
I think I've...
I'm taking this one.
This is a fun item.
And I do value fun.
Imagine if we had gotten brimstone or something though.
That would have been the bee's knees.
Oh!
Ah, wait.
I lost a heart.
Ah!
We gotta kill him first.
Target acquired.
Nice.
Who's next?
Okay.
We may have to wait for the configuration here.
This is awkward.
Fuck!
Oh, I did it!
Nice!
Yoho!
We're back in business!
We got the health up!
No!
Horrible item!
Wait, is it?
Let me see.
Uh...
Horrible item.
I'm coming back with mana.
I mean, energy.
Battery.
Maybe.
Maybe?
Maybe I can't make it.
I may have to go to the shop, but then I need a key now.
That was so lucky!
I totally nailed that!
Oh!
Love this item.
Okay, ah...
I shouldn't have picked that up before I went.
I mean, I should have gone inside the cursed room before picking up the blue heart.
Damn it, man.
I didn't see it in time.
Okay, this one's not happening.
We gotta kill him.
I just don't trust like that.
Swallowed penny!
Sure!
Why not?
More money is always good.
No, I killed him accidentally!
I could have had an extra item in here.
So, am I cooked on keys here?
It looks like it.
Unless I go into the cursed room.
And maybe get lucky.
No!
Wait, did my fucking...
Dude...
What's it called?
Where is it?
The varicose veins just ruined the whole thing for me.
Can you believe that?
Uh...
I don't think I want this.
Huh.
I got a bomb.
We could look for a secret.
Could be here.
Ah, but wait a minute.
This is like a thin room.
I don't think that works.
I think it's up here.
No, but there's a thin room there, too.
Ooh.
Maybe next to the shop.
Right here.
I'm gonna use my last bomb, I believe!
Ah!
Okay.
Let's move on.
Honestly, all things considered, this is going well.
Ooh!
I kinda wanna speedrun!
But maybe I'm too late for that now.
Let's try and go fast.
Caleb!
Nice.
We got a key, okay.
Wait, how come I ha- Wait, hold on.
Where did I get this?
I have no memory of where I got this.
Weird.
No clue.
Two oclops?
Double spawns?
Okay, well...
Maybe not yet.
Coupon!
I gotta take it!
And what is this pill?
Black creep?
Nobody cares.
Piggy bank, three coins...
Ooh, that's pretty good, actually.
Um...
Oh!
Ha-ha!
Amazing luck there.
I think I do need to heal.
But let's not do that now.
Uh, wait, wait, I could- I could actually reroll in here.
Hold on a minute now.
Rerolls all pedestal items in the room.
Hmm.
Red candle launches the directional flame attack.
Nah, I prefer my D6.
I'll come back and reroll this later.
Oh, well, let's kill this guy first.
It's gonna be a tough one!
Ah, rip.
Okay, you know what?
I think it's gonna kill me when I try to do the deaths list.
Only do it when it's feasible.
No!
Okay, we gotta go back and buy that heart now.
I think I'm close to death.
At least we got a bunch of money out of this!
Haha!
Because we got hit so much.
We go back.
Yoink!
Just to play it safe.
Also gonna take this.
Sick.
Uh, we can double bombs now.
Four bombs.
Ahhhh.
Actually, it's fine.
Okay, so my demon chance is 9%.
It's not very good.
Chop!
Oh, kill this small guy?
It's too risky, I think!
Bomb him!
Wait, did he just eat the bomb?
What happened there?
The bomb disappeared.
That boss was a little bit, uh, sketchy.
Plus one lock, soul heart, two keys.
Ahhhh.
I may actually wanna reroll that.
Yeah.
I mean...
I'll come back.
So we can reroll the boss item, and we can reroll the shop item right now.
Multiple possibilities.
They call me the sniper!
Ha ha ha!
Yeah!
Wait, we got battery out of that.
Cool.
Oh, I love when there's only one enemy.
Nevermind, there's two.
Come on then.
See ya!
And we got a chest out of it!
Okay, nevermind.
I love death's list.
It's great.
Oh, I hate this item too!
Guys, we're gonna reroll this one.
Yes!
Poison good.
And we have good luck as well.
So this will actually be huge.
Let's go over here.
Calm down.
Got some battery there.
Not bad.
Nee-nee-nee-nee-nee-nee.
Nee-nee-nee-nee-nee.
This is gonna be a tough one.
No!
The poison!
Eugh!
It ruined everything!
I had it all lined up, man.
That was terrible.
Three bombs?
I could look for a secret.
I think I know where it is.
Right here, boom.
They call me the investigator.
Ayyy!
Oh wait, I was there already.
This way now.
Dude, it feels great to play this game again.
In fact, just playing anything.
No, I killed the speeder!
Death's List is like...
It's a lot of feel-bad moments, you know?
But it's also a lot of feel-good moments, so...
The tower.
Not interested in that.
I have good damage!
Yeah.
The Wheel of Fortune, I guess we could...
I guess we could.
A little bit.
Come on.
Taking all my money!
Okay.
That was totally not worth it.
I'm gonna use this later on.
Oh no.
This may be too risky.
You got poison though.
Okay, this guy on top next.
Sick.
Actually professional.
Wow!
You can't touch this.
This one's gonna be a tough one.
How do I do this?
Ah, now impossible.
Actually impossible.
Wish I could see my HP.
Ooh, pills are good though, pills are good.
Can I still grab it?
Nice.
Okay, I need a little bit more battery.
Come on.
That's gotta be possible.
One more room.
You cannot do this to me.
Fine, I'll keep doing this.
I need a blue heart.
Uh...
Ugh.
No.
Extension cord.
Wait, electricity arcs between Isaac and all familiars.
Arc steels...
Wait, I don't have any familiars.
So, no thanks.
Dude, this sucks!
I'm leaving.
On a jet plane.
Too bad we can't reroll, huh?
What a bummer.
Unless we can find battery somehow.
Hmm, not in here.
Yeah.
Move on!
It's unfortunate.
But it's not that bad.
And we get a soul heart, you know, for a buffer.
It's something.
I guess my plan is to go kill...
Isaac.
Either Isaac or Satan.
I haven't decided yet.
Oh, this guy.
Why?!
Fuckin' hell!
I hate the poops!
Buffer gone.
It was nice knowing ya.
Uh...
I guess we wanna go...
To the bottom right first.
That looks way better.
Okay, come on.
We can do this one.
Okay.
Take it easy, take it easy.
Oh shit.
Who's next?
You.
Sweet.
Okay, you're next.
Sniper.
Sniper!
Hahaha!
God Gamer.
Wait, we just gained...
2.5 range?
That was the reward?
Dude, death's list is...
fucking bonkers.
Aha!
We gained speed!
This is the best item in the game.
Change my mind.
Lil' Gertie?
Eh...
I don't like it, guys.
I'm gonna...
reroll it to Lil' Spewer.
Uh...
Reluces puke attack.
I don't like it either!
Wait!
Spawns one random pill when picked up?
I like that.
Copy the last pill?
That's health up!
Oh no, it's luck.
Okay.
That's still fine.
I like it.
Uh...
We can get there, actually.
But that's gonna cost us two bombs.
Hmm...
Let's wait.
Screw!
Oh, that's so huge for me!
That's gonna...
up my damage so much.
Thank you.
We also gained some demon chance there.
Wait, if I do this...
there's two bombs...
Yeah, fuck it.
Let's do it.
We're probably gonna find more bombs.
Yeah, there we go.
Okay.
Oh, I'm actually in trouble down here.
Thank you.
Lucky Penny!
Dude, I have so much luck!
Seven luck!
That's crazy!
I'm the luckiest boy in the world.
Also, uh, we should probably go to the boss now.
Before we...
Wait, did I already lose my...
I think I already lost my chance.
Oh, crap.
No!
Okay, thank god it's down there and it's a bad one.
There was no chance of that happening.
Bring it on!
Peep!
Shit.
Wow!
Okay.
I mean, that didn't go too well, but it's okay.
Speed and damage!
That's two out of three on spun as well.
I do not remember what the max rank of that does, but surely it's good, right?
Oh, he almost walked on that.
Oh my god, sip.
Oh.
It's...
This is going great, man!
For the first game?
In over a week?
Oh, crap.
Okay, so this guy needs...
Ah!
I lost almost all of my HP just now.
It's not going great.
Uh, additional secret room?
Yeah.
I have 37 money anyway, so it's fine.
Oh, god.
There's no way this is happening, right?
Unless it counts for the whole snake.
Yeah, that's impossible.
Nice healing.
Good.
And where's the shop at?
It's up here.
That should have actually been my priority.
Since I have so much money.
Stand on my creep.
Oh, you asshole!
Oh.
Uh, we could...
We could reroll that.
We may not actually need it.
Look at all the money we have, right?
Yeah.
We got a lot of money!
What the fuck?
Uh...
Actually, take it.
We're gonna buy everything the game has to offer today.
Oh-ho!
Pills!
Massive!
And battery...
Oh, hold on.
Maybe I, uh...
I could reroll that, actually.
Let me see...
This one...
The moon...
Ooh!
Ah, but we've been there already.
Rip.
We're gonna save it for next floor.
Uh...
I'll buy a key as well, I guess.
Now, battery...
I could use that on...
Uh, let me think.
Did I have another item I could reroll here?
I don't think so.
I mean, I can reroll the pills.
I may want to do that, actually.
Options!
Two rewards...
Two rewards instead of one.
I like that one.
And then we take this.
And then we're ready for more.
I'm gonna blow these guys up.
Thank you.
I may do...
Curse room.
Ah, I have three hearts.
It's a little risky, isn't it?
Let's just move on, honestly.
I feel okay.
No, no, no, no, no!
Actually, no.
We clear everything.
Dude, already paid off so much.
Oh, I should have opened the chest, I guess.
Amazing!
Oh, shit!
I keep forgetting that I can only take one of them.
Mmm...
Blow this up.
Shouldn't waste all my...
Bombs.
Totally worth going back, by the way.
Now we have a buffer for the next floor, and we have a moon as well.
In fact, we're gonna have two secret rooms on the next floor.
Let's go!
Hell yeah!
It's going well.
Speedrun is, uh...
It's not gonna happen, though.
We're too late for that.
Battery in there, that's cool.
But it's not a big one, it's a small one, so...
Two keys for that?
Probably not the best.
Okay, so, chest.
This way.
Oh, we can totally do this one.
Ah!
No, I killed one of them accidentally!
Why is it so difficult?
Oh-ho-ho, you bastard!
Uh, I'm not gonna do that.
Nope.
Blow it up.
Massive.
Sweet.
Uh...
Oh, that- that gave me luck?!
Incredible.
Pulse worm, no thanks.
Don't care.
Ah!
Yeah, that was risky.
May have been worth it, let's see.
Dude, more luck!
Okay.
This is like perfection.
But all the time.
Uh...
Wait, wait, what the hell is this?
Hold on a minute.
Right!
I'll be back, maybe.
Maybe I'll be back.
Now I don't have any bombs, though, and there's two secret rooms.
Let me actually do this.
Rich get richer.
81 coins, somehow!
Jesus.
Okay.
I need a shop.
This one's gonna be tough.
Somehow that was lucky.
Ah!
Sick.
Nice!
Nailed it, nailed it.
Uh...
Wait a second.
Why...
Wait, hold on.
What did I note down last time?
Uh...
Fight room, fight room.
There.
Opens with full red hearts.
Discovering...
I was so sure about this.
Opens when...
Have blue hearts.
Huh?
Okay, now I'm really confused about this.
Drowsy is actually not bad.
We'll save that for like a boss.
Fight room, let's do it.
Uh, wait.
They don't have any exes on them.
I thought I could kill them in order here, but I can't.
What am I taking damage from?
Oh, it's the homing ones.
This is a tough room.
Ah, I should've opened the chest.
Mistakes were made.
This one's gonna be a doozy.
Assassinator!
Get him!
Nice!
I can't hit him!
Who's next?
You.
Is it you?
It is you.
Dude, why are they so difficult?!
Blows my mind!
I have 99 Luftballons.
You know I'll be using my money here.
Dude, that's huge!
Yeah!
Where's the shop?
Haven't found it yet.
I guess...
We can take one of these.
Slows everything for the room.
Dude, that PhD has gone wild.
Ever since we got it.
We could potentially step...
Wait, wait.
It's my little, uh...
Familiar changing appearance?
He used to be red.
Now he's black.
Okay, let me just, uh...
Move on.
I don't wanna waste all my money in case we get a shot, right?
Uh...
I'm gonna play it safe.
Not bad.
I guess it's my luck.
Like...
If I get super lucky, I get rich, right?
Like getting the right lottery numbers.
I'd love to find a pedestal though.
Exactly, so I can start using my...
D6!
Oh god.
Oh, I messed up the...
Thing.
Oh, we're not done.
I don't know what just happened there.
Monster manual.
I hate both of these.
Reroll!
Scissors.
Isaacs...
Nope.
Punching back.
Uh...
Maybe okay.
I think I'll come back, honestly.
Shitty items.
Like, I had four attempts at a good item there, and none of them were good.
Blows my mind.
Yeah, now my familiar is doing black goop.
Instead of the green goop, and red goop.
My shot speed is off the charts too.
Kallus!
Oh!
Yes!
Abso-fucking-lutely.
Poor man's flying.
Damn, I messed it up.
Ah!
I didn't mean to!
I was gonna pick up the chest.
I misstepped.
Oh!
Oi-oi-oi!
I'm low HP!
Uh...
No.
I need to, I need to...
No, actually it's fine.
The fallen.
Okay, so this guy.
Oh god.
Oh my goodness!
Backstabber.
I don't like that very much.
But I'll take it and then go back and reroll the other items, because there's a higher chance of getting something good there.
Oh!
Nevermind, nevermind, nevermind!
Hold on, take care of these first.
Definitely rerolling in here, I can tell you that.
False PhD.
Necromonicon.
Okay, here we go.
Lord of the Pit.
Abaddon.
Speed-oh, flight!
Guys, flight is pretty good, but that leaves us with three red hearts.
This one is...
Replaces all heart containers with black hearts.
Chance to fire fear tears.
Chance increases with luck.
Hmm.
Both of these are good.
The thing is, I have Callus right now, so maybe I don't need...
flying anymore, you know?
I think I'm gonna take this.
It also gives me speed.
Yeah.
This may...
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
I could get both.
I could do both.
We can do both.
I'm taking both!
I'm so naughty!
It was so naughty, I don't deserve this.
I can't believe I just did that!
Ah, we gotta play perfect now.
Okay, but we can fly now, so it's fine.
It's fine.
It's gonna be totally cool.
We got Drowsy.
Let's not run into things accidentally now.
Guys, we're gonna go gamble and get a bunch of soul hearts.
Trust the process.
Trust me.
More speed.
Come on.
It's gonna blow up at some point, which is gonna be unfortunate.
Come on, baby.
Oh yeah, my Familia changed again.
My Familia is white now.
Uh, wait a minute, where's my...
Wait, I still haven't found the shop!
Ha ha ha!
Dude, what?
Let's go find the shop.
Oh, we can take this now.
It's probably in here.
Yeah.
Mom?
Are we good?
No, we're not good.
I thought we could buy things!
Crap.
I guess we don't need Callus anymore, yeah.
Uh, why not?
Okay, back to gambling.
Trust the process.
It's okay, it's okay.
Actually, maybe I'll take this.
Come on, man.
Be good to me.
I hate to say this, but I think we may actually be too fast.
Like, the speed is too high.
I'm not gonna be able to control myself.
Oh, shit.
Oh, nice.
Actually, I love this.
I love this.
Where's my blue hearts?
Slows everything for the room.
That's huge!
Yeah, baby!
Oh, crap.
Is that what I think it is?
More speed?
Okay, fine.
I'll take it.
I'm at max now.
It's okay.
It is what it is.
Uh, we gotta keep rolling.
And that was all she wrote.
Um, drowsy.
Okay.
Nice.
I think we're good to go now.
Boss room is all the way over there.
Wish I could open this without taking damage.
Uh, actually take this instead.
Yeah.
Give me that.
What just happened?
I don't know what just happened.
Something spawned and died.
Ah, I can fly now!
We're totally cool.
Uh, you want bombs?
I got bombs for you.
How about...
Wait, wait, hold on.
Actually, something's wrong here.
Uh...
Which one is it?
Replaces all...
Heart containers?
Oh, no, nevermind.
I thought what this meant was every time a red heart dropped, it would be a black heart.
But that's not how that works.
I'm not gonna give you all my bombs.
Just most of them.
Huh.
Immune to poison?
Not bad.
I don't like that it's dark, man.
That's...
That's no bueno.
Huge!
He played safe.
Now it's making circular circles.
Oh!
Reroll!
Why did I spend all my money?!
Guys!
If I hadn't spent my money.
This could have been so good.
Wait.
I forgot my D6!
Ah!
It hurts.
It hurts real bad.
I cannot believe it!
Dude.
How is this real?
Fucking hell.
Well, this gambling machine better give me something good down the road.
That's all I'm saying.
Whew!
Uh, here.
I can't believe I left behind the D6!
I messed up the order.
Uh...
There's no way we can do this room in order.
I just don't believe.
What's this?
The hermit.
Uh, that's the one that takes me to the shop!
SHOP!
Actually!
But wait, uh...
We've already been to the shop.
Can we kill this guy, please?
Are we done?
I keep forgetting I can fly.
Yo!
We need this money, actually!
Huge!
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
Ayy!
We almost had it!
I couldn't see anything!
I was blind!
It was dark!
Damn it!
That's massive!
Blue hearts right now are worth...
so much.
Okay, let's just kill him.
No reason to be a hero here.
I didn't mean to pick that up.
Any tinted rocks?
Where are you?
Oh!
Fuck me!
Dropping from the sky!
Like, how are you supposed to do anything?
Uh...
Aw, damn.
There's a step room in case we want to do that.
I don't want to do that.
Money is good!
35, man!
We can go back and reroll like crazy.
And we have steam sail as well.
It's actually kind of fire!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Trying to kill them in order.
It's a mistake!
Just kill them.
Don't try to style on them.
What is it with these drowsy pills?
Too many of them.
Technology too.
Wait, what is this one?
Uh, left eye will continue.
I think it's good.
Man, we lost a lot of attack speed though.
I will say that.
Okay, boss is here.
And it- This is mom.
This is mom.
We're not gonna engage yet.
Actually, I could.
No, I- No, no, no.
I need to finish this first.
Uh, back to the shop.
And what was this?
The hermit...
Oh, I guess I can use that.
Take me back.
The hermit.
Reroll.
More options?
I mean, isn't that a little too late now?
I'll take it though.
Ace of clubs?
That's bombs, I think?
Wait, what?
What did I just get?
I don't understand what I just did.
Okay, whatever.
Notched axe, battery, and...
Magic fingers...
Bat- What the hell, man?
No.
Oh!
Ah!
But wait, this is a problem now.
Uh...
Oof.
This, this, this...
The problem with this is, I need those blue hearts for myself.
You know?
Um...
Let me see.
Stars deplete and can only be charged by picking up soul hearts.
And...
Oh, man.
Wow.
Parts consumed to charge the box or not added to Isaac's health meter.
This is the risky play?
I'm taking it!
Uh...
Pay to play.
Okay, I don't like this.
It's okay.
It's gonna be good.
Trust.
Trust in the process.
We still have a room we didn't clear.
Oh, my God.
Okay, maybe the technology is actually kind of fire.
Yeah.
Time for boss.
I feel good.
Maybe we'll look for a tinted rock?
Nothing here.
Oh, uh...
Give me this one.
We're gonna activate I'm drowsy in the mom room.
Actually, blow this up.
You know what?
I should be blowing all of that up.
Because they have a chance to drop hearts.
So if I find more skulls like that, you know?
We can also look for a secret.
Let's do that, actually.
We have 19 bombs.
There's no reason not to do that.
Nope.
Maybe here.
Dang.
Maybe...
Here?
What?
Could be here.
You gotta be shitting me.
Right there.
Oh, come on!
Okay, what?
Where the hell?
I've been all over the center.
Maybe, like, here.
Dude.
Okay, let's try going this way, then.
There we go!
Finally.
That money is actually huge!
We can go back and re-roll.
Okay.
Let's do that.
We can also blow it up, by the way.
In case we need to...
Oh, actually, speak enough!
Shit!
Uh, re-roll.
Oh!
I re-rolled too much, or what?
More luck?
Why not?
Luck.
The jar?
Eraser.
Spawns red heart pickups?
No.
Man, this sucks ass.
I guess we can re-roll a bit more.
I mean, uh, gamble.
Hematemesis?
Sets Isaac's health to one red heart.
Spawns...
No, thanks.
I mean, that's...
I'm maxed already!
Okay.
Unfortunate.
I think it's time to leave.
And do mom.
Here.
And there.
And before I do...
I blow this up.
Before I go in, I gotta take a piss.
Be right back.
Okay.
We're gonna use drowsy here.
And we're gonna kick her ass.
Isaac!
Oh, yeah.
Good damage.
Dude, drowsy's actually kinda...
Good!
I mean, I mean, really good.
Wow!
We're gonna take, uh...
Let's take...
The Polaroid.
Guppy's paw.
Permanently res...
Okay, hold on.
Let me destroy this first.
Too bad I don't have...
The fucking D6 right now!
Huh?
Uh, guppy's paw...
Remove...
Uh...
This...
Is...
This is all gonna go into the box.
I think...
Ah, but wait, wait, wait!
Removes one HP to...
When I pick this up, I'm gonna...
Lose one red heart.
And then when I use it again...
Then it doesn't really work.
Yeah, so this is actually kinda...
Not good.
It's bad.
Well, shit.
Too bad.
I have to charge up this box.
Ideally, I really should be killing these guys in order.
Just for a high chance of getting, um...
Like a heart, you know?
And you know, the...
Technology's gonna help a lot with that.
No!
I missed it up at the end!
Damn!
That was beautiful though.
No!
No.
Ah, yes!
Dude, they are so tanky!
Close one.
Ooh, oh, oh!
Oh no, it doesn't work!
It doesn't work, of course.
I keep forgetting that.
We may have to...
Actually, I can just sit in here, look!
The guy we need to kill is down here somewhere.
He's gonna come any second now.
Oh, he's up there.
Get him!
Got him!
Now this guy.
Follow me, follow me.
He's stuck.
Okay, now it's this guy.
How am I gonna do that?
Damn it!
Give me blue hearts.
I got...
Nice!
Attack speed!
Huge.
Oh god, not the eye.
This may be too risky.
Yeah, it's too risky.
If there's an eye, we just kill everything.
Don't even question it.
Just do it.
I can't believe we actually did that.
Uh...
Oh, actually, these are good.
I can come back for another one.
Oh my goodness!
Okay, who's next?
You're next.
Okay.
Got him.
And you.
Beautiful.
Now I pick up the chest.
Honestly, bombs are good because...
Higher chance of finding secret rooms.
And blowing up blue flames, right?
Ho ho hoi.
Uh...
I think I want chest.
Yeah, oh nice!
Huge.
Okay, we're charging.
It's being charged!
Where are you, sir?
No!
Okay, good, good.
I was confused for a second there.
I shouldn't release him.
Copy the last pill?
Uh...
Verp?
Oh, okay.
Another verp!
If I find a health up, that's gonna be mega huge right now.
Wait, uh...
Plus one luck?
Even more luck.
I think I'm gonna...
I'm gonna do this now with the drowsy pill.
Blasto-cyst.
I'm gonna kill them in order as well, cause I'm such a G.
Okay, now it's boss time.
You cannot focus on the little guy.
Huge.
This is crazy!
Oh!
It got messed up at the end!
Fuck me!
I cannot believe that.
Oh, soul hearts!
Okay, charge my shit.
Uh, this is...
Joker...
Empress...
I don't wanna go in there, cause I can't really pick anything up in there, right?
Aw, man.
I do wanna take a peek, though.
Yeah, this is...
Yeah, that's bad!
I'm gonna die if I take this.
It ain't gonna happen.
I'll be back.
Maybe.
Uh, actually keep this pill on me.
This is actually so good.
Okay.
The box is, uh, half charged.
Let's go to the south.
For the warm countries.
Do we have any tinted rocks here at all?
I'm trying to look for X's in Texas.
Uh, it's not gonna blow up on me?
Okay.
Uh, I don't want hematemesis.
Why am I being risky?!
Guys, I think it's over.
I think it's over.
We have no HP!
One hit and we're down!
And we can't even buffer up with anything, cause we've got the box on us.
I may have been too greedy.
I admit it.
We need a miracle.
A gosh darn miracle.
Yeah, keep the drowsy one actually.
Uh, teleport...
No.
Keep going.
It's gonna be fine.
If I see a crazy room, we pill immediately.
No question.
Don't be a smartass!
Oh my god.
Uh, here...
Shit, not these guys!
Fuck!
I was so scared, cause I couldn't see them off screen, you know?
Okay, pill!
We're pilling this one.
I take no chances.
Oh my goodness.
Come on, blue heart me.
So I can charge my stupid box.
Nooo!
Ah!
I'm too greedy.
Too greedy!
Ah...
One more.
One more with Isaac.
Honestly, I lost the run when I forgot the d6.
That's just what it is.
It was unfortunate that that happened, I would've had it otherwise.
You know it, I know it, everyone knows it.
Dude, I feel like everything is in slow motion now.
After having played Isaac with so much speed before.
This feels weird.
Good start here.
Unfortunately, we have Curse of the Lost, so I don't know what the hell.
Actually, go in here.
I believe!
Nice!
Tears up.
Okay!
I'm not mad.
I like that.
Perhaps we can...
We're very slow right now.
Dude!
It's okay, we can afford to take HP damage on this floor.
Uh...
I shouldn't pick that up yet.
I know it may seem crazy, but trust me.
Trust me.
Nice!
Fuck.
Oi, oi, oi.
I don't have a lot of speed.
This is gonna bite me.
In the ass.
Oh ho!
Actually pick it up now.
We have another backup.
This is actually a good start, guys.
Libra.
Speed, less tears, more damage, less range.
Um...
Stat upgrades are balanced among all stats.
Uh...
You know what?
Why not?
Getting a bit of speed back is actually kinda important.
Guys, a steam sale in the first...
In the first one is actually nuts.
I'm gonna blow this up.
That means I can buy the present as well.
Well, most likely I can.
I'll be back.
This has potential.
This has a large potential.
Ha!
He walked into the thing.
Come on, give me one more coin.
Uno mas.
Why am I green?
Actually, I'm sort of half green, half...
I don't even know what that is.
I'm bagging myself in a corner.
Run!
Shit!
If I didn't have speed there at one, I think I may have taken damage.
No tinted rocks.
So far, so good.
We cannot do that.
These guys are so tough.
I cannot lose damage.
Or HP.
How the fuck...
What is the strategy for these guys?
Like, I have yet to crack that.
Yeah, this is not gonna help me now.
Uhhh...
We got seven coins.
I'm gonna go back.
We're gonna buy from the shop.
This way.
I forgot what was in there.
Oh yeah, the gift!
Mystery gift.
Spawn a random pedestal item from the current room's item pool.
So basically, this is what you wanna do, guys.
You wanna use this first.
And...
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
It's an active.
I would have to...
Hold on.
Uh, let me think.
If I take this...
I go there...
I spawn another one...
I come back.
Yeah, okay, okay.
This is what we're doing.
Yep.
We bring the gift first.
Oh, I have no map.
Right.
I wanna find more goddamn...
Tinted rocks.
Wait, what was the boss?
This way, I guess.
There we go.
I don't wanna lose my buffers to this guy.
I need my buffers for the next floor.
I could use some bombs on him.
I have six bombs!
Holy shit!
Actually, why not?
Play it safe, right?
There you go.
Enjoy.
Ah, it only hit one of them.
You also have to remember, as soon as they die, they release...
Toxic shit all over the place.
It's very dangerous.
No!
It made us!
Okay, little guy's angry.
Maybe we can get into a cheese configuration here.
Potentially.
I don't wanna be too close when he dies.
Sick!
Okay!
We can actually get rid of little Steven if we want to.
So check it out.
This is what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna do...
Uh...
Wait, let me think.
If I reroll this into something I don't want...
We also have the world.
Ah, but I can't see anyway.
Ooh, but I do have...
I have four bombs!
We could potentially, even though I can't see the world...
Guys!
Mystery box...
On the secret room.
If we can find it.
But I need to really map this out then.
I need to consider all my options here.
So wait, this is where we started.
Okay, so we have this room here.
Okay, that's a no-go.
This is a no-go.
No-go.
Uh...
Maybe up here?
Potentially.
Uh, wait, wait.
I'm gonna try.
Shit!
Okay, it's fine.
We have three bombs left.
What about down here?
So there's also this...
That way there?
I-Dude, I- Without the map?
I can't do it, man.
Like, I...
I'm sorry.
I'm too stupid.
I need to see the map.
Maybe here somewhere.
Could maybe be there?
It's also down here.
So this...
Where's that lead?
Eh?
Actually...
Fuck.
I'm wasting all my bombs.
Try this one here.
Alright, suck my ass.
We're going for the original strategy.
This way.
Okay.
Okay, so watch.
This is my- This is what I had in mind.
We do this.
Okay.
I don't really like either of these.
So then we go back and we can reroll both.
This is the big brain play here.
In fact, there's even a battery in there, but we don't have money for the battery.
Oh shit.
Can I somehow scrounge up three more coins is the question.
Maybe in here.
But that's- Now we're getting into risky territory.
That's maybe taking it a little too far.
Okay, so give me this.
Now we go back.
So now we have double chances of getting a good item, right?
In fact, I wouldn't mind getting two HP up items.
That would be amazing.
The lost debuff is absolutely the worst debuff in the entire game.
It is.
It's not even close.
Sick!
That's what I wanted, baby.
Okay, now I'm definitely gonna go to...
Whatchamacallit.
Maybe I can even step a little bit.
Nah, stepping is too much.
Nothing?!
I've never seen nothing.
That's wild.
Literally nothing.
That is crazy, bro.
Okay.
Moving on.
Time for second floor.
It's going well, actually.
I feel like I'm making all the right plays here.
I keep looking for the...
For the kill order, you know?
But I don't have that anymore.
Hey, come here.
Uh... Oh!
Guys, we're gonna do it!
Because we have the buffer.
It's genius.
Larry.
This guy's actually kinda tough.
We may have to be ultra careful here.
Destroy the poops.
Oh, I split him in two.
Hoi!
Nice!
I think we got it!
Mega huge!
We're gonna take the snack?!
We- oh wait, I don't have a reroll ready.
It was a trade-off.
If I had, you know, continued on and lost my buffer and lost some HP, I maybe wouldn't even have gotten a demon room.
The pact.
Ooh, I like that one!
Uh, Gympie.
Chance to drop a soul heart.
That's also good!
Guys, I'm taking both.
It's not a brimstone, but it doesn't have to be.
Yoink!
Heh heh heh!
Oh.
Almost went for me there.
I'm happy with this outcome.
I look like a Gymp now.
A latex Gymp.
Oh.
Oh!
How can you avoid that?!
They were closing in on you from two sides, it's impossible.
Nuh!
Oh my god, really?
I need money.
Nuhhhh!
Ahoy!
I'm good, I'm so good.
Actually amazing.
Wow!
Next level.
Oh, there's pills, man!
I will need to find...
Bombs.
What's that?
Chance to spawn a copy of a card pill or rune?
I like it!
Imagine we get a health up pill, you know, and it spawns a copy.
Oh!
Tinted Rock?
Definitely.
More health!
Yeah, we're going full demon mode this run.
Oh!
See, I could use the world, but I don't have any bombs.
So right now, that's a mistake.
We're going to save it.
Envy!
He's the one that does the...
I think.
Nope, never mind.
Let's steal the guy.
I need shot speed.
I could have sworn I didn't touch him there.
Like, his hitbox is larger than his model.
We're going to reroll.
Technology zero!
Tears have small beams of electricity that arc between them.
I like that!
Definitely taking that.
Insane reroll.
D6, baby.
We're never going to leave behind D6 again.
Nope.
So there's also a shop, but I don't have any money.
But I could take a look.
I have so many keys.
Oh yeah, right.
We have the steam sale.
I could...
I could pill max.
I'm going to pill max.
Ah!
At least we know what that looks like now.
And we have health to spare.
So it's actually fine.
Moving on.
We got one buffer, which is good.
We also got the world.
Of course, find being secrets.
No bombs though.
Can't do it.
No drinks.
Curse of the labyrinth.
Whatever.
Is that what I think it is?
I was about to say we got a laboratory.
But that's not it.
I'm not really feeling the technology zero here.
Okay, I'm feeling it.
I'm lacking damage.
Like, it looks pretty and all, but there's no damage behind it.
Mercurius.
We got speed, tears, damage, and range.
Most doors remain open in rooms with enemies.
The effect does not apply to boss rooms.
Got it.
Thanks.
Oh look, I got cool feathers on my hat.
Okay.
Technology zero is very good against small enemies that are numerous.
That's when we like it.
I guess more range is better with technology zero too.
So the effect lasts longer.
Uh, yeah.
Explosivo.
That's not bad actually.
That is pretty good.
I wonder though...
Let's say I have technology zero, right?
And I shoot two tears and they have this arc between them.
I wonder if the arc itself has a chance to apply Explosivo.
Because if that's the case, then it's good.
We're gonna test it.
I didn't have mana to reroll anyway, so fuck it.
I'm gonna save that for the inevitable demon mode room.
Which is all the way up.
I should actually go there.
ASAP.
Yeah, let's just hit the...
Wait, this is a double trouble.
Ooh, uh...
I can easily go to this treasure room, reroll, come back to the boss and have enough energy for rerolls.
Let's do it.
Oh no, I'm stuck in a corner!
I hate when that happens.
Well now our buffer is gone, so rip.
Great!
All my dreams are gone now.
Mom's perfume.
I don't... I don't... I don't mind it, honestly.
I like it.
I don't wanna reroll it.
Like, it's good.
Why is it every time I play Isaac and I have the d6?
I never get shitty items that I wanna reroll.
Like, I always wanna...
Stick with the items.
Okay, ten coins now.
I think the, uh...
The arcing electricity is definitely applying bombs.
Or is it?
Oh no, no, it's not actually.
The bomb is gonna...
It's one of the projectiles that form the arc.
So it doesn't work like that, unfortunately.
I'm gonna open this.
Uh...
Yeah, let's go to shop.
Ooh, that battery is huge.
Okay, trust.
Ah!
It's not too bad, I guess.
Oh, this is totally worth.
Yeah, yeah.
Technology zero is only gonna get better the more damage I get and all that.
Uh...
You know what?
I don't like this very much.
Too much RNG.
Uh, secret room here?
My keys...
I'll give you some.
Ooh.
Range down.
Well, okay, okay, so...
Every single stat item now is gonna be distributed.
Uh...
So I get how that works.
I was wondering about that, but now I get it.
So, positive, negative, you know.
Oh!
Like, I like this!
I don't wanna change it!
It's good!
Yeah.
Chance of getting a demon, though, is only at 9%.
There's a chance, though.
Come here, you.
Wait...
Oh, right.
Oh!
Oh, so close!
Mega Man!
Dude, the bombs are good!
Explosivo.
I
like it!
I don't wanna switch!
Oh, god.
Get blown up, nerd.
Okay, this one...
I like it.
I like the stock.
I do!
I...
I don't wanna re-roll!
What is my current, uh...
Endless Nameless?
I like...
Okay, let's just go with that, I guess.
Uh...
We...
We're not done here.
Unfortunately, no demon.
I just wanna use my D6!
I want it to be off cooldown.
Like, all these rooms are wasted energy now, you know?
Uh...
Actually, yeah.
I was gonna destroy the mushrooms, but that's a nice side effect.
Oh, fuck!
Okay.
Ooh!
I...
Nice!
That's a good one.
The thing is though, I don't think I wanna spend all my money.
Nah, I'm gonna blow it up.
I'm gonna save my money for the next floor, with the shop.
Yeah, we're done here.
There was nothing in the shop here that I wanted to buy anyway.
This was a crazy double trouble...
Level.
Now.
We have a huge buffer!
Time to find the boss room ASAP.
Oh no, I hate this already.
Oh, I can just leave.
Ha!
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
This is actually kinda nuts.
Use the world.
Dude, I'm gonna beeline the boss!
See ya later, nerd!
Aha!
This is insane!
See ya!
Oh god!
Why can't I enter?
Also, I went the wrong way anyway.
The boss is actually not here, it's further up.
I hate this room, I hate this room, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it.
Where's my actual shop, man?
Come on.
Also, let me check something real quick.
Increases devil angel room chance.
We have a 100% chance right now.
Here we go!
100% devil!
We really have to fuck this up.
To not get a devil.
Oh!
It's not looking good.
Wow.
This guy is like on steroids.
Uh, supper?
You know what?
I like it.
It's okay.
It just means we can get more devils.
Nooooo!
I'll reroll.
Hey!
The list!
We're back, baby!
Okay, time to explore the rest now.
Oh, you first.
You first, then you.
And then, uh, mom is here.
And, you know, all kinds of things.
Yeah, that's not happening.
Give me that.
Load up!
Okay, I've got six bombs left.
Maybe I shouldn't go too crazy.
Oh, no!
Dude, what the fuck is hitting me?
I'm scared!
Okay, we're done.
Whew!
Okay, okay.
I'm dying over here!
Okay, who's next?
No, really.
Who's next?
I'm so confused!
Where's the next one in the list?
I don't get it.
I killed the right one.
It makes no sense.
Yeah, this is broken.
The death list doesn't work on these guys.
Mom's Eye.
Chance to fire additional tears from the back.
I don't like it!
Hot Bombs.
I'll be back.
Huh?
Okay, I don't know what just happened there.
The death list is finicky as hell.
Oh, right.
Huh?
Oh, random mushroom, maybe.
Finally, we did it!
For hematemesis.
Great.
And... get blown up.
Okay.
It's going better now!
They're unpredictable movement.
It's messing with me.
We're going to go reroll.
Now that we have battery.
I did not take it, right?
Okay, good.
Midas touch!
Petrification turns enemies to gold untouched.
Deals contact damage.
I mean, I already have so many coins.
I don't really need it.
The problem is, I don't think I can get enough battery to...
...come back, so fuck it.
It's not great.
What was this pill?
Range down.
Fight room!
Oh, come on!
You little fucker.
I'm having trouble right now.
Okay.
One buffer.
At least that's something.
For the next floor.
Uh, let's get in there.
I got plenty coins.
I would love a plus one HP from him.
I can just stand here.
Bro, what is it with the keys?
Come on.
Okay, you know what?
You're clearly not willing to give me anything other than keys.
I'm gonna save the rest for another shop.
Okay, so it's mom time.
Mom- I've been pretty good at keeping track of where mom is.
Oh, yeah.
Guys, I have a plan.
Check this out.
We're gonna- we're gonna get to max battery?
Ah, wait, never mind.
We can't go back from mom anyway.
But my plan was...
To get max battery.
Skip rooms until we get to...
The boss.
Uh...
Reroll.
Come back.
Clear the rooms.
Get battery again.
You see what I mean?
Blood of the Martyr.
I LIKE IT!
For fuck's sake!
Why am I getting so many keys?
Keys, keys, keys, keys, keys.
Nothing else.
Oh, wait.
Wrong one.
Oh.
This one's gonna be a little hairy.
Woo!
Yeah, nice.
Heh heh heh.
Oh god!
The gravity!
Wait, somehow we're still doing it.
Ho-hoi!
Nuts.
I like the rooms with few enemies where the deaths list can actually do something.
It brings me immense joy.
We got shot speed out of that.
Huge.
Actually, I'm gonna blow these up.
Nothing.
Wonderful.
I've been very unlucky with pills in this run.
There's nothing good ever.
Okay, if I wanna gamble.
Perhaps I want to.
Shit!
I shouldn't have even tried.
You know?
To kill them in order.
When they're so fast and unpredictable.
Calm down, calm down.
I'll take this.
So we get two out of three on moms.
And then we're gonna...
Ah, do we reroll here?
Let me think.
It's not guaranteed that we will have enough for potential demons.
We take this one though.
Like, I could...
Hmm...
There's a battery, I guess.
Member card!
I like that one!
Battery?
Wait, if I reroll now, I wonder if that works when there's no item.
There's a pedestal.
Hold on.
It says rerolls pedestal items...
in the room.
Oh, yeah.
It doesn't say pedestal.
It says pedestal items.
Okay, so maybe not.
But we have this down here we can explore.
Black card is nice.
There's no pedestal items here.
But I can reroll.
Ooh, this is potentially really, really good.
Notched axe.
Wow!
Whoa!
Safety pin!
Hello?
That's good.
I need to take that.
Damn!
I'll be back maybe.
Later, when I have more money.
That was a solid shop.
And now I want to beeline it to the boss if I can do it.
We can use the d6 again.
For wasting too much energy.
Actually, I can just go.
Yeah, just go!
Oh wait, I can't go!
For some reason now.
Why?
The door was open.
Oh, whatever.
Wait, it's mom!
We can't get out again.
Ah...
What is that skull on the floor?
Oh, it's mom.
Uh, grab the Polaroid.
It's still good.
Wait, I wonder if I could have rerolled the Polaroid.
Wait a sec.
Why didn't I try that?
I should have tried that.
What did I get?
Oh, luck.
Not bad.
Oh!
Lightbulb!
I mean, I always run around with full items anyway.
I mean full, uh, you know what I mean.
Energy.
Oh yeah.
Now this guy, and then this guy.
Oish.
It's getting a little risky.
Damn.
Cartridge.
I need flying or something, otherwise this creep is gonna murder me later.
It really is.
Bob's bladder?
Oh no.
What's happening here?
My damage is good.
Sort of.
No, it's good.
It's good.
We still have demon chants right now, so if we hurry...
Maybe I can run through the rooms.
Oh, don't pick that up.
But I would really have to haul ass then.
And not get hit by anything on the way.
Uh, we can try this way.
See ya.
Oh god.
Oh no.
Mom?
I mean, boss?
Where?
Nope.
Oh no.
This is risky.
Bip!
The devil is fine.
Duh!
There we go!
Found it!
This is actual gaming right here.
We can't get hit now.
Oh, blastocyst.
Come on, focus!
Fucking phenomenal!
Speedball, yes sir!
We're gonna go in here and reroll now.
Lord of the...
Ooh, wait, wait, wait.
Uh, Lord of the Pit.
Uh, I need to take these out a little faster.
Okay, Lord of the Pit is, uh...
So, speed, tears, damage, range...
Grant's flight!
Oh my god, I gotta do that.
And then we reroll.
Spirit of the night.
Ah!
Too bad.
Why you gotta do me dirty like that, man?
Come on.
Why?
Uh, what was that?
Oh, Wheel of Fortune.
Let's go up here.
Sweet.
Wow, two blue hearts?
Don't mind if I do.
Another one!
Damn!
Oh!
Ha ha!
I'm not gonna take it!
Too bad I didn't have enough energy there, huh?
Wait, does that mean the room is still open?
I can just go back when I have enough energy?
I thought it would close.
I mean, we're gonna try that.
Let me see.
Wait, I'm flying now!
Ha!
It's so hard to get used to.
Nah, it's gone.
But maybe there's a way we can get teleported back again if we find, uh...
What is it, Joker, right?
There's a chance.
A slim one, but it's there.
Uh...
Give me that one.
Okay.
We can also look for a secret room.
Professionally done.
I like that one.
I messed it up.
How did you hit me?
Huh?
Oh, okay.
Weird enemy.
Oh wait, I can fly now!
That means we can grab...
the heart.
And potentially other things too.
Uh...
Placing a bomb also creates a small pool of high damage and creep.
I don't care.
Let's just look for it, right?
Uh...
Give me that one instead.
Could be there.
I feel it.
Unfortunate.
I wish there was a way to get back to, uh...
the devil room.
Perthrow!
I like that even more.
And that was that.
I am out of here.
It's going well.
So I honestly do not remember how we even get to Isaac.
So we have to...
We have to go up at some point.
I think this may be the floor where we do it.
Because we have the Polaroid, right?
So we should be able to go up.
That was unfortunate.
Oh shit, dude.
My pills have been shit the whole fucking run.
I found pills.
Pure bad luck here.
I don't know how you don't get hit by the fucking inanimate objects.
Like, it's...
the hardest enemy in the game.
How are you not dead?
Oh, it's a boss.
That explains it.
I messed it up.
The tower...
You know what?
Why not?
Hehehehe.
My...
Sodas.
Up to four uncle like to pick us from the previous floor.
Respond to starting.
Let me reroll this.
Great.
Didn't do nothing.
So wait.
How does this work again?
Starting room of a new floor.
So I guess I will have to...
have this on me for the next floor.
Uh...
Let's do that actually.
That's probably something we missed, right?
If we can even get there.
Because I am...
I have four HP.
Actually I have two HP.
And I'm dying here.
The game is too hard.
Uh...
Do I want this?
Nah.
Healing is huge here.
Very good.
Uh...
11% demon, man.
That sucks.
I like that Death's List wanted me to do the boss first.
Yeah, like that's gonna happen.
Okay.
Not too bad.
Why is there no item spawning here?
What the fuck?
That's...
That feels bad.
Not even gonna get an item?
What's that about?
Come on, please health up for fuck's sake.
Okay, not yet.
It's not meant to be.
I'm gonna need some buffers here.
Teardrop charm.
Nah.
Not feeling it.
I have a lot of buffs.
Okay, D6 is ready.
Uh...
Maybe I can find another item.
Pedestal, that is.
Not the eye!
I mean, that was actually impossible because he was inside.
How would you do that?
I can't believe I did that.
Great list.
Ah!
That is so hard to do.
Ah, give me that heart actually.
And this one.
Okay, we're almost done here.
Yeah.
Let's get the hell out.
There's actually a curse room.
And we have the hearts to spare.
It's worth.
Unfortunate.
Time to leave.
I feel like it's going well, but also horrible at the same time, you know what I mean?
It's not good.
And this D6 may as well not have existed because...
There hasn't been an item I could use it on yet.
That would have made sense, you know?
Aha!
Buffer!
Vibrant Bulb.
I guess I can wear that now.
And then switch it out later.
Uh, fuck all of y'all.
I'm going this way.
I'm looking for the boss.
Yes.
Search, search, search, search.
Oh, I can do this one.
Health down again!
Come on.
Uh...
Yo, actually massive!
Good shit.
I shouldn't kill them.
Not yet.
Uh, here...
Dude, where's the boss at?
Not in here.
This is such a weird strategy.
But I like it.
There was nothing back here?
There is something back there.
There we go, there we go.
That's it, baby.
Okay, here we go, here we go.
Uh, we got D6.
Oh wait, this is Isaac.
I forgot.
Oh shit.
Oh, well.
Okay.
Isaac's gonna be...
He's not gonna have a chance against me.
I'm too strong.
Easy money.
And there we go.
We did it, baby.
Wait, there's more!
Isaac's tears has appeared.
I keep forgetting there's more.
Oh wait, the ultimate reroll, guys!
Uh, multidimensional baby.
Eyesore.
I hate all of these.
It's actually crazy, I hate all of these.
Then again.
Three tears and a cone shape?
That's not bad.
Actually.
You know what?
I'm taking this.
I'm gonna reroll.
Sprinkler!
Pop!
Replaces tears with eyeball shots that can bounce...
No, no, no, no.
Dry baby block shots and deals.
That one is actually good.
I'll take that.
I'll come back and reroll these.
Especially with my technology zero, man.
It's even better now.
What just happened?
I just healed or something?
No effect.
I mean, there's gotta be some secret with that pill, right?
Dead cats.
So this is gonna reduce me down to one heart and that's it.
This is just bad.
Unless it also conserves my blue hearts.
If it conserves my blue hearts, then it's good.
But I don't think it does.
If I get more blue hearts, I'll try it.
Never mind, I'm losing my blue hearts.
I'm getting them back.
Bro, what the fuck is going on?!
Gimme.
I actually need to do this.
I need battery.
Damn!
Mom!
That is the most aggressive mom I've ever seen.
Dead Onion!
Wait, hold on.
It reduces a bunch of stats, but plus tier size, piercing tiers, spectral tiers.
It's not that much, like, lowered stats here.
I think this is okay.
It's good.
Yeah, and bigger size as well.
Oi!
Ah, we're probably not gonna be able to sustain that.
Contagion.
Uh, yeah.
Oh, we should go back and reroll, by the way.
There's two items we can reroll right now.
Oh, in here.
Proptosis!
Tears gain a large damage bonus, but have much...
Ooh!
Uh, let me think.
That's actually okay, I think.
Teleport.
Nah.
I'm taking this.
Yeah, look at that.
We still have massive range.
It's fine.
Okay, and then we're gonna go up here.
Actually, grab this.
Scapular!
Ooh!
Wait!
When damage down to the last half...
This is very good with, uh...
With Guppy, actually!
That's like the ultimate combo!
Whoa!
I like it!
I'm actually gonna pick up Guppy, I think.
It depends what we find.
We find a lot of, you know...
Blackhearts or something, then not.
Okay, see.
This is good.
Dude, what's with all the items?
I can reroll this.
Wait, we also have Perthrow.
Big Chubby!
Eh...
I don't like that.
I will reroll it again.
The moon!
Oh, I like experiments.
Totally worth!
Take me to the secret.
Oh, no.
I killed the wrong one.
C-section.
Replaces tears with a charge.
Attack the fire's floating fetuses.
These fetus shots last a few seconds and hone in on enemies.
Hmm...
Could be good, actually.
Oh, wait, no!
Oh, I missed the charge thing!
Oh, actually...
Oh, that's actually kind of cool, then.
You can hold the button.
Hey!
Okay, I like it.
I almost instantly regretted everything I just did.
Dude, this is insane!
Holy shit!
I like the C-section!
Mysterious liquid.
Tearsleaf creep where they land!
That's good.
Let me see how that works.
Well, they don't really land anywhere, do they?
Oh, okay, they land at the end.
Okay, maybe we're not that good.
Definitely exciting.
Dude, they are homing in on enemies!
Obsessed fan!
I like it!
Let's go left.
Oh, we can also reroll this.
Number two.
Baron continuously for three seconds drops a butt bomb.
I don't like that.
Ooh...
More luck?
Sure.
Like, I'm dealing a lot of damage.
The halo!
Wow!
Plus one health!
Insane.
Definitely taking that.
Can I...
I don't think I can reroll anything anymore, so I may as well just take this.
We have run out of rerolls.
I don't even... can I...
Man, I should have gotten the keys.
I forgot about this part here.
So you get these keys from the angels.
Let's go to the boss.
Uh...
Hmm...
No way.
No way, Jose.
Here we go.
Oh, I can barely see his attacks.
Because of all the crap I have on me.
Okay, he did.
He did.
I guess I should just continue on here.
Yeah.
Keep going.
We're going down.
I forgot what was down here.
It's been so long.
The D20 has appeared.
Nerd.
Something wicked this way comes.
I'm getting a lot of unlocks!
This is great!
Hell yeah.
Oh crap, that's actually dangerous.
Uh, I've got coins.
Yeah!
Insanity.
More like that.
Oh, that works too.
Thanks.
Wait, I could have rerolled that if I wanted.
But it's fine.
Dude, the C-section is...
Kinda wilding, isn't it?
It's gonna be annoying.
Eh, it's too annoying for me.
So many bombs.
Dude, I could just go destroy...
Skulls here, you know?
With all these bombs.
Not even that bad of an idea.
Yeah, look at that!
Doubles my coins!
I'm rich!
Let's see what we get.
Satan!
I'm gonna fuck him up so hard.
Bomb for you.
I mistimed that.
Yeah, okay.
Bro has no shot.
Strange attractor.
Enemies pick as well attracted to Isaac's tears?
Yo!
That's also good for me!
They're gonna get smacked!
Damn!
Woo!
Yeah, they're gonna run into them now.
They can't... they can't leave!
What is this room?
I... I can't even see what's happening here!
Oh!
Inanimate objects.
Of course.
Are you actually kidding me?
Loki!
They're gonna die so hard.
I mean...
Ow!
Okay, I like this one.
We're taking that.
That's just another shot at life, right?
Uh...
Oh, not larger.
The good news is, at least I can see my character more easily.
I'm dead!
Okay, bro.
Time to die.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What is happening here?
Wow.
Wait, he's dead already?
Haha!
I thought that was first phase!
Bruh!
No problem.
Skip that.
Dew has appeared!
Dude, we unlocked, like, five items in that run.
Five!
We're gonna continue here.
Look at that!
We got, uh...
Satan...
No, wait.
Uh...
We got...
Isaac, I guess?
We killed Isaac, and then we killed...
Delirium.
So...
So, Isaac is the cross.
And Delirium is the other sort of page with the circle on it.
Okay.
Uh...
What I need to do next is to...
You know, I'm actually gonna take a picture of this.
Because otherwise I will...
Oh no, it's not.
Uh...
Do this.
And we're gonna go in here.
Like this.
And then we're gonna say...
Mo...
Uh...
Heart.
No, Mom, I...
Heart, I guess.
Right?
And then we have...
Uh...
Isaac.
And...
That'll be Delirium.
There we go.
And then the last one here is...
The Beast.
Uh...
And then we do...
I forget how this works.
Let me just put it like this for now.
I can add arrows later.
There we go.
Now we know.
Good to remember that.
Okay.
Uh...
Next up we're gonna do...
Who do we not have a lot of achievements on?
Judas.
We haven't even...
Wait.
We only have the Beast on Judas?
That's kinda crazy.
Damn.
Let's play some Judas.
So...
Judas has good damage.
But one HP.
So...
Everything...
Is gonna rely on us getting a nice HP upgrade from the boss.
No bombs.
Fortune cookie.
I don't like that.
Actually, maybe it's okay.
I'll run around with that for a bit.
I'll come back for the damage book.
Oy!
Oy oy oy!
You are dark inside.
Ha ha!
Okay.
Try again.
I thought by the way that I...
I took half a heart of damage.
I don't know how I died instantly.
I really don't know how I died instantly there.
I should have taken half a heart of damage.
That made no sense.
So...
Rainbow heals you!
I will never get a streak going.
Never.
It will never happen.
I am banned from that.
That's just sad.
I really just want to restart.
Like the worst item in the entire game.
And maybe Sprinkler.
And again, I haven't really tried Sprinkler that much.
Who knows, maybe it's actually okay.
No, it's not.
It's shit.
Oh, come on.
No way.
Not good.
Hey, we have this.
Yay!
I should have activated my damage in there, actually.
Any tinted rocks?
No.
Oh no, not this sort of room.
This is the end of me.
Okay, we're good.
Scary, though.
Oh wait, no, no, no.
Oh no!
This room is gonna fuck me!
I used that.
Totally worth.
Whew!
Good thing I had that card.
I'm using this here.
I gotta do it.
At least it's not the jumping dudes.
Because those guys always get me.
Okay.
I got two bombs.
No tinted rocks for me at all.
I got six coins as well.
Maybe I look for a secret.
Also, I've been definitely taking money out of the bank more than I have been depositing.
So that's not great.
I think right here.
I thought wrong.
Okay, there's one other opportunity.
I see it clearly.
Here.
So from in here.
That's surprising.
That's really surprising.
Like, where else could it be?
I don't know.
Actually, it could be right here.
Damn.
That was unlucky.
Little horn.
Have I ever fought you before?
Okay, I do remember something like that.
What the?
I'm gonna die.
Oh, I don't like this little thing.
I don't like that.
Get this shit away.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Oh!
Come on.
I'm being a little risky here.
We're going for the kill.
Oh!
Yes, HP!
Massive!
We're back.
We are totally back in the game.
What a fight.
Okay.
That got my blood pumping.
Now we actually have a really good chance of taking it all the way to the end.
Just because of that HP.
Boop!
Come here.
Come to me.
I know you want to.
Okay, I think I may...
No, I'm gonna go up here.
Yeah, just keep funneling through one by one.
Oy!
Okay.
Da-da-da-dum.
Ow!
There goes my demon.
I'm gonna go get that...
Get that half a heart.
We still have 50% demon actually.
It's not too bad.
And you know what?
We're saving for angels.
We can't do demons on low HP like this.
Dude, this red guy right here can...
Piss off.
Clean.
And a lucky penny.
Oh god.
No way!
Get the heart, get the heart.
There's a heart here somewhere.
Fuck.
Don't tell me I'm cooked because of that.
Oh no.
Oh shit.
I don't mind this actually, but only when I find a bomb.
There we go.
Secret up here.
Actually, we're gonna go get the heart now.
Before anything else.
There we go.
Maybe I should do boss now.
I mean, now that I have at least 50% chance.
Actually, it doesn't matter if I'm saving for angels.
Oh no, it's gonna be a Steven reward.
I hate this boss because of that.
Actually, use this.
Cheese configuration!
Yeah!
Stay mad.
Okay, secret room time.
I actually do like Steven a little bit.
I like that he has homing tiers.
It's not too bad.
Like, it could be worse, right?
Ooh, very nice.
Uh, yes.
Damn.
I have 16 coins as well.
There's no way.
Oh no!
Uh, okay, there's a heart I can grab, so that means I can do curse room.
Black- oh, nice.
Ooh, that's really nice.
I hate floor curses.
Oh yeah, baby.
That is massive.
Now we get the heart and we get the hell out of here.
Wish I had a key though.
Maybe I can find a key, uh, by breaking open something.
Somewhere.
Where could I do that?
Man, that's so cruel.
Oh wait, let me get that heart actually.
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, I can blow my way in!
Oh yeah.
Very nice.
Okay.
Uh, let me see.
Broken watch, every fourth room is slowed by- That- that is pretty good.
Uh, you know what?
There's so many shitty items in the shops.
I'm gonna take this.
Because if I reroll with a bomb, it's just gonna become a shitty item.
Um, I know it.
And then I'm gonna regret it.
If there's a good item in the shop, you take it.
Immediately.
Because it's rare.
I could also grab some more money here.
Uh, two bombs for- Yeah, actually that's worth.
Why did I just get a key?
Wait.
60% chance for bomb to drop- Oh!
That's why.
Huge.
Let's go baby!
Judas!
He's got the HP.
He's got it.
And now we're going for angels.
Still no angel chance though.
Oh, that's unlucky.
That's very unlucky.
That that just happened.
So this is two.
This is three.
We're gonna grab that later.
That is actually huge.
Oh!
Okay, we're gonna come back for that.
And we will come back for that.
We will!
Come back!
No forgetting!
If I forget that, I'm gonna uninstall the game.
And then probably reinstall it because I'm addicted, but you know.
But I'll definitely uninstall it.
Just for the act of doing it, you know?
Man, that's unlucky.
Oh, there you are!
I thought it was an empty room.
One?
No, that's zero.
One.
Yeah, come on then.
I'm not a big fan of this one.
But okay.
Wait, how is it slow already?
I'm counting wrong here.
Maybe the empty rooms do count then.
Yeah, they must count.
I'm taking damage here.
I really shouldn't take damage.
These spiders are confusing me.
Making me think they're enemies!
What is hitting me?!
Hello?!
Are they enemies or not?!
This way.
Dude, I don't trust...
We need HP!
This is bad!
Come on, spiders!
Attack!
Do your thing.
Oi, oi, oi!
Ah!
Oh, I'm definitely buying that heart, I think.
Yeah, I have to.
We got a plate safe right now.
This is a very risky situation we're in.
63% on demon.
Not that we're gonna take a demon, but you know.
Just saying.
Oh, shit.
It's actually a good slow room.
We're gonna...
We're gonna try and see if we can get a slow on the boss.
But it's probably not gonna happen.
Not that I think about it.
Choo!
Kill the little guys!
Ahoy!
Dude, there's too many little guys.
That's for you!
Hey, hey!
Become my friend!
Eat your friends.
Okay.
Oh!
Bandage, baby!
Yes!
That is massive.
I feel so...
And we...
And we get the eternal heart!
Let's not forget.
I'm not done clearing, though.
Clearing everything.
Everything must go.
Oh, god.
Definitely eating this.
Experimental pill.
I hate it!
Great!
At least we have the eternal heart still.
That's...
That's something.
Makes me feel better.
Ah, wait.
We're done now.
Look for secret, maybe!
This looks like a candidate.
Let me have a look here.
I'm so good.
Battery, huh?
That's not exactly what you wanna see.
Here's the thing.
We have some money now.
I'll go back to shop.
It's going well!
Except for that one pill I just ate, but, you know.
That happens.
Now, you see, I could...
Blow this again.
But let's not do that so many times today.
It's too much.
I will...
I will leave.
There's nothing I want.
I'll save the money.
Next shop.
Would love to get a bit more speed.
I feel slow.
Cheers, guys.
Oh, that sounds weird when it slowed.
I kinda wish it would stay slowed down, the soundtrack, for the whole floor.
Oh, crap!
Oy!
Wow.
I'm playing this so safe right now.
Oh!
I'm gonna try and get, uh...
Keys from angels.
Yes.
Battery there.
Dude, when are angels happening?
Because...
Right now, I only have, uh... demon chance.
And it's like, third floor or something.
Oh, god!
Nice.
Non-spike on that, good.
Uh...
Yeah, I got 17 coins.
Spider-Man!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Yup!
Taking that.
And...
Yup!
Taking that too!
The run is safe, guys.
The run is safe.
I can't lose.
Even get some more money there.
Uh...
Two lovers.
Oh!
Not bad.
Aye, aye, aye!
That was bad.
I'm embarrassed that I did that.
100% demon.
Oh, whoa!
Jackie!
No!
You cannot jump up on the...
There we go.
This is an important moment, Jackie.
I can't take damage now.
Ha!
I ran into the...
Because I'm bad.
I gotta be ready for his jump.
What the hell is that?!
That's new.
Please kill him!
Oh, thank god.
Health is huge.
Dude, okay.
We have so much health right now, we could actually go for a demon.
No, no, no!
No, we have 40% angel now.
Let's not take it.
I will...
I will stick to the...
No, Jackie.
She keeps jumping up on my keyboard.
One of these days, she's gonna kill me.
Like in the game, I mean.
I really should just close the door.
The problem is, during summer, it gets so hot in here, that closing the door is pretty much not an option.
Otherwise, I will...
I will surely die.
Of heat stroke.
It's gonna be 34 degrees next week, in Denmark.
I'm not looking forward to that.
It is actually impossible to play games in that heat.
If you don't have an AC.
Speaking of, I bought an AC!
During last week, I was like, on the internet every evening going, Should I...
Should I fucking...
Spent the money on this shit?
And I finally pulled the trigger on it, and I don't even know if I'm allowed to have it.
In an apartment, you know?
Because it makes noise.
It has like an outside unit.
So, I don't know.
I may have to return it, we'll see.
I need to see how loud it is.
I did read reviews and all that, but...
Nobody's fucking testing the sound levels for some reason.
Like...
You have one job as a reviewer, you know?
Pisses me off.
And then they're sponsored as well, of course, so you can't really trust anything people are saying.
I fucking hate what the internet has become regarding that, man.
You cannot trust anything anymore.
You know those top 10 websites?
Top 10 best vacuums you gotta buy in 2026.
All links are affiliated.
Yeah, great.
Now I don't trust anything you're gonna say.
Like, fuck off.
And yes, I am so old that I get excited by vacuums, okay?
I've been looking at top 10 lists of vacuums.
So shoot me!
I'm at that stage in my life.
Where vacuums are...
Very exciting.
Come on, get him out of here.
Oh, we got a pill here?
Shit!
It's fine.
We're actually okay.
Don't panic.
It's okay.
I don't really understand hematemesis.
Niii!
Okay, we still have buffers.
I heard the...
You heard it, right?
Aw, man.
Okay, what's the status here?
Status is...
We're gonna leave.
We're done in this part of the world.
The run is actually good.
Really good.
I also should use my book more.
I keep thinking I'll save it for a rainy day, you know, and then I never do.
That's the problem there.
Did I have anything else I could buy?
I don't really want this.
Eh.
I'll come back.
To another shop.
In the future.
I'm tempted by the...
Wait, why is that still open?
Is it this one?
I don't know why that door is open.
Maybe it is only when...
You enter and leave.
You know?
That's the thing.
No, no, no.
That's not true.
Because I've seen it disappear even though...
I don't know, actually.
That's a mystery.
40% angel chance.
Surely we can get this done, right?
Without taking damage.
It's a risky one.
Oof.
Oh no.
Dude, this room is hard.
Like, what do I do?
Impossible.
I got the shittiest of all the rooms.
There's nothing I can do.
I hate when that happens.
And now my angel dreams are dead.
I will never get my angels.
My keys are gone forever.
Sad times.
Instead of 16% chance though.
You need to calm down, son.
Wishbone.
Ooh, yeah, actually.
Not bad.
Oh, this is bad.
I gotta bomb it.
Shit.
What the hell?
Wishbone just worked.
Yeah, this room was killer.
Oh, that's good.
Heal me up.
Uh, Mongo baby.
Why not?
Okay.
Got some healing for later.
Ugh.
I have no more bombs.
I used them all.
Man, where's this boss at?
It doesn't matter at this point.
The Hank man.
That's interesting.
Could come in handy.
We have 21 coins as well, so a shot would be insane.
Dead end.
Oh.
I'm being assaulted.
Jesus.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
I think this counts, and this is- No, it's not even a shop!
Man, this is just bad.
I feel terrible.
Oh, what am I gonna do with all this money?
Oh!
It's not been going too well the last five minutes.
Do I have more?
No, I don't.
A magician.
I think I'd rather have this.
Oh, this is the- I mean, that's pretty good as well.
In fact, I think it's better than what I have.
Because I can just keep retrying.
Especially on low HP when you're a glass cannon, you know?
Nice!
I- That's fine.
See, I could have retried that there.
I don't know why I didn't do that.
We found the shop and treasure.
Okay, good.
The cage.
Oh my god.
Wait, wait.
How come we only have 4% angel right now?
Hold on.
I thought it was only the first time you got hit.
That my chances got reduced.
But I guess it's not.
We can't get hit now.
I'm using the magician.
Oh wait!
The hourglass counts?
With the- With the slowing time on the- You know, the fucking- You know what I mean.
That is actually insane.
That's a great combo with him.
Whoa.
Ah, me.
Come on!
This guy is crazy.
Like...
He has so much HP.
What the hell?
I'm afraid he's gonna jump.
Here he comes.
Oh my god!
I'm so fucking angry right now.
Okay, so this- This should be it.
If I go back now, That should be the slowed room.
Bro.
Are you serious?!
It's over.
Yup.
It slowed.
Come on, baby.
This is it.
Nevermind, it's not slowed.
I miscalculated.
Great.
I'm gonna have to use bomb on him.
You know what, dude?
Time to uninstall the game.
Like...
It's over.
Out again.
Now it slowed.
Oh, man!
That jump is fucking crazy.
Okay, he's doing that now.
He's doing that.
This is the one.
Come on, homing.
Homing, homing, homing.
There we go!
Only took, like, nine tries.
Didn't even get an angel.
I'm moving on.
I've had it with this floor.
Okay, it's mom time.
There's an arcade and we are flush with money.
Could be an option.
Die!
And there goes my angel.
That's funny.
Funny.
Okay, it doesn't work twice in a row.
Got it.
Now I know.
Genuinely...
Going for angels?
Not even worth it.
I could have had seven demon deals at this point.
It doesn't make any sense.
Like, it is insane.
It's not like the rewards from the angels are that good anyway.
At least not compared to the demons, I guess.
I mean, it's kind of similar.
Like, you would think for the amount of effort you put in to fucking get to a single angel room!
That every item would be, like, game-changing.
You know what I mean?
Like, it would change the run.
Not the case.
Wait, what?
Oh!
The hell is that?
No.
Uh...
This way.
Alright, we don't have enough HP.
Where's all the blue hearts at?
Cricket set.
Ooh, that's good though!
Good damage!
Also, what were these buttons?
Oh.
We're embracing the...
What do you call it?
The glass cannon.
41 coins!
Can we get a proper shot this time?
Scary.
Uh...
A black heart!
Not bad.
Wait, what do I have now?
I have shot speed now?
When did I get that?
I don't even recall getting that.
Oh, now we're cooking!
The game hurt me.
Not bad...
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Oh, it's the worst shop of all time!
Wow.
I wanna find the boss and move on.
It's just cruel...
To keep giving me money when I can't spend it on anything.
It really is.
Makes me feel terrible.
Also...
Where is this boss?
Okay, here we go.
Mom!
Good damage.
Damn it.
25% angel chance here.
There is a chance, guys!
Maybe luck smiles upon us.
Are we gonna be blessed?
Damn.
Unfortunately not.
Uh, let's do...
Oh, let's take the negative.
Let's go down this time.
I'm feeling it.
Utero.
I'm just gonna jump in a second here.
Oy.
The enemies that jump scare the living bejesus out of me.
Wake up.
Oh wait, I should've used...
Aw, I forgot about the hourglass.
I could've hourglassed that.
Too bad.
Realized too late.
And now there's no shops anymore, so this is...
Not great.
Okay, let's see if we get anything good in here.
Yep, so you know what that means.
We're getting the fuck back out here.
That was a horrible room!
Woo!
That was the ideal use case.
For that.
That was a trap.
Temperance.
Uh...
I don't need that.
I have so many spiders.
Actually, stay at range.
Don't waste the spiders.
I...
Kinda wanna...
revert time now, actually.
Cause that was kinda...
Ooh!
Holy crap!
I've never seen this!
That's all my keys!
Uh...
This one we want.
Ooh, yeah, we want that one.
That's the good one.
That's the good stuff right there.
Oh, yeah.
I'm also gonna take, uh...
Let me think.
This one.
Now we have...
Bookworm!
Feels good, yo!
And we'll come back for, uh...
The hourglass, I guess, if we wanna check out sketchy rooms.
Hoi!
Wait, telescope lens.
Chance of a planetarium spawning.
Uh...
Wait, wait, wait.
What did that say?
Something about the womb?
They can spawn in the womb and corpse.
Okay.
Maybe it's...
Okay, let's actually do that, then.
I mean, maybe we get it, right?
Oh my god.
There goes all my black hearts.
Should've had my...
Hourglass with me.
Shoulda, woulda, coulda, right?
Easy to say.
But you best believe I'm looking like a hawk.
At my energy levels here.
So I can use my...
Satanic Bible.
As soon as it's ready.
Damage is good, though.
Like, we have good damage here.
Ghost baby.
It's gonna take us to three out of three unconjoined.
That's worth.
And we get angel.
Fuck.
It's good, though.
It's good.
Wait, uh...
Paschal candle.
Milligrams.
Stack into...
It's not that great.
Like, this is a shit item.
Okay, let's blow up the angel.
We're gonna get keys now.
Oh, nice.
This was an insane room.
Very good.
We're not done, though.
You gotta beep shittling me.
You know what we need?
We need a mystery box.
We go back to angel, and we get another one.
Imagine.
I think this floor is cooked now.
I can't even see where I am.
So, you know what?
We're leaving.
Going down.
This is a messed up room.
Oh, man.
I love conjoined.
One of my favorites.
I mean, look at this.
This is beautiful.
What a work of art.
And we get battery there as well.
Nice.
Oy!
I'm taking that immediately.
Because we got a buffer.
It's okay.
Arcade, you know I'll be spending money here.
Wait, is this battery, man?
Ooh!
Oh, guys!
Guys!
We're gonna be filling up on black hearts.
In fact, maybe I'll only give him...
Oh, he gave me a battery as well.
This is massive.
I suddenly feel better about everything.
One of the best arcades of all time.
Okay, and now we're gonna stack up on two.
We don't have shops anyway, right?
So who cares?
He can give us more, right?
Yeah!
Ah, we're done.
Okay.
Nice!
Please!
Not bad.
I mean, now I'm ready.
For anything.
Man, that guy has HP!
Whew!
Unfortunate that I got used here, but you know.
I need to remind myself what this candle actually does.
Stacking tier bonus for each room cleared without taking damage.
Right, so basically, don't suck.
Got it.
Wait, am I pushing back?
What's happening?
Why did the tiers sort of do that?
Dude, it's not going well.
That's okay, it's okay.
Shadow baby!
Whoa!
What is that even?
Wait, I forgot, which one did I have?
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Wait, where's my...
Pola.
Oh, negative.
Right.
So we're going down.
There's nothing else I want to do on this floor.
Actually, treasure room.
We do want treasure room.
I can't believe I haven't found that yet.
Maybe also secret room.
Dammit, I keep getting hit by something.
Let's go south.
Like, my damage is good, but I feel like it should be better.
I need more.
It's not quite there, you know?
I need a bit of shot speed, I think.
Shot speed or fire rate.
Both would be nice.
Jackie, you can...
No, no.
I will soon feed you.
It's funny.
Like, cats must have, like, some sort of internal clock, you know?
Because she knows when she's gonna get fed.
Oh wait, I need to go this way.
Nice.
Let me check out this pill.
Oh my god, really?
Oh, come on!
I've had such bad luck with the pills this run.
Oh no.
Oh, okay.
That's not too bad.
Another one?
I feel like when you get Satanic Bible, it's like almost an automatic win.
It is just that good.
Changed my mind.
What are we doing here?
Oh, buttons.
Fuck!
Yeah, that didn't go well, did it?
I'm telling you, inanimate objects are the hardest bosses in the game.
What a room, holy crap.
Mom had no chill.
A pill.
Please be health up.
Shit.
Oh, that was scary!
Speed down, of course it is- Oh!
Planetarium!
A new one we haven't seen before!
Neptunus opened the floodgates?
Grants a rabid fireburst of tears that charges up when not firing.
The burst depletes while firing, lasting for up to three seconds.
Okay.
Oh yeah, I see it.
Let me see.
Oh my- Dude, this is broken?
Wait, why does it keep going?
Oh no, no mind.
It doesn't.
It's good.
That is good.
We got the damage.
I think now the run is safe.
0% angel chance though, I don't like that.
Oh, it's because I already did the boss, I guess.
Okay, that door's closed.
We could do...
I!
But I don't wanna do I, you know?
But I could do it.
Not gonna.
Left.
Uh, down!
We're going down into the depths.
We're gonna fuck up everyone we see.
We're gonna make fun of them.
We're gonna bully them.
Ruin their day.
I felt like running into that in case you were wondering.
Wait, what the?
Open your mouth.
I'm not sure what just happened.
Nothing in the past five seconds made sense to me.
Dude, this, uh...
This item I have here...
Neptunus is insane.
Ohoy!
Damn!
Oh no, not these guys, I hit them.
Somehow it worked out.
Wait, do I have spectral tears?
No.
I think that the...
Yeah, look, my thing is charging up at the full speed.
And the room is in slow speed.
So this is even better.
With the...
What the fuck is it called?
The broken watch.
Okay, health up!
Come on, health up!
I can see you forever.
Okay, I like that one too.
What the?
Allows...
Adds one holy shield at the start of each floor.
Nah.
Crystal ball.
Reveals the map and drops a card, ruin a soul heart.
Increases the chance of a planetarium appearing.
Yeah, why not?
Oh,
wait, if I pick this up now, I wonder if it will...
Yeah, it gives me one, so then I take this.
Oh, never mind, it goes away again.
I thought I was being a little smart there.
Oh!
Wow.
He came at me fast.
So wait, I'm not going in yet.
We need to slow that down.
I'm pretty sure that's Satan.
So, let me see.
One, two, three, that's perfect.
Uh, I don't wanna...
Scary.
That's one.
Two.
Three.
And now we go boss.
And boss is gonna be slowed down.
Or sped up if I'm really unlucky.
Wish me luck on this one.
Nice, we're slowed.
He's not gonna stand a chance.
Come on, then.
There we go!
And here comes...
The man himself.
Yo, Neptunus is insane.
Oh, don't run into him.
You dumbass.
Aye!
I'm playing this so bad.
His feet are so unpredictable, it's crazy.
Wait.
I thought there was more after this.
Uh...
Okay.
Oh shit, there's more!
Alright, now we're cooking.
Judas Tongue has appeared!
Okay, what is that?
I don't have the keys!
Aw, not the list again.
What do I need this for?
Aha!
I like that.
I've never seen that.
But based on the look of it...
It looks like one of those things where...
When I drop a bomb, it'll become...
You know, the brimstone bombs.
So yeah.
I don't really want that.
Assuming, of course, I'm right.
Could be wrong.
Uh, it's not actually looking too great with the HP.
Uh, we may actually be cooked, guys.
This...
This is looking pretty bad.
Dude, this room is insane.
My damage is shit!
I thought my damage was good, but it's not.
Oy, oy, oy.
Tough love.
Okay.
I do have three luck.
Wait, why is everything...
Oh, never mind.
It's because this is the fourth room.
Okay, we gotta stock up on these items here.
I mean, health.
I can see forever is actually cool.
Just beat down, ew.
Sprinkler.
Come on.
Anything but the sprinkler.
I feel like the game is doing me dirty right now.
I see you up there.
Okay, there's a boss here.
I think that's Mega Satan.
I'm not ready for that.
We need to slow that down.
So this is, uh, one now.
Two.
There's something about the...
Like, look at this!
Maybe we need a shovel.
Probably a shovel.
Okay, so three is over here.
Teleport.
Okay, now we go.
There should be a slow down boss now.
Okay, I...
This is gonna be...
Oh, the lamb!
Dude, how actually?
How?
Whoa.
Oh god!
Which way?
Okay.
Uh, no.
Wait, I can go down though.
Wait, wait, what is this?
The curved horn has appeared.
I am scared.
Wow.
I need to focus on getting HP right now.
Just playing it safe and...
Getting that HP.
I feel like I need flying or something.
Jackie.
I'm gonna feed you in just a second.
You can wait...
Five minutes.
I'll have to go right after this.
Wait, let me actually quickly see...
Tch!
She has food in the bowl!
She wants the fresh food, I guess.
Okay, so we're at three hearts now.
This is gonna be a tough one.
I mean, so far so good.
Uh, strength.
Yeah, definitely want that instead of what I had before.
No spikes, no spikes.
Okay, good.
How come he doesn't die?
Oh, okay.
Oh, man.
We need to have, like, a buffer of health here.
This is not gonna be enough.
Magician could be massive.
That may actually be what we need.
Okay, there's a boss here.
Let's not do that just yet.
Holy fucking shit!
I don't know what's happening.
Wait, are we done in here?
We're done in here.
Not inanimate objects!
Blue hearts, maybe?
Come on, come on.
This is the shot we have.
There's one.
Unidentified, come on.
No.
Wow.
One more, please.
That is so unlucky.
Okay, 4 HP now.
Nice.
What is this room?
I mean, I don't mind.
More of that, please.
This is how I'm gonna get my battery.
Sorry.
No!
Whoa!
It hurts!
It hurts my soul.
It really does...
Actually, blow these up.
Damn.
Panic button!
Nah.
I don't know how to deal with this eye.
The fool.
This is an evil flame.
That was art!
Pure art.
Belongs in the museum.
Hermits.
Woo!
What the hell?
What is even happening?
That's a weird room, isn't it?
I don't like this room.
No!
Why is it always right before I get my last charge that I have to get hit?
I will never build up my...
parts here.
Ever.
What I need to find is one of those beggars that give me...
Battery.
That would be the thing, right?
Shit.
I've tried almost every pill in the game.
On this run.
And I've yet to find a single good one.
Lost cork.
No thanks.
That's a champion.
Oh.
Wasn't anything special.
Oh wait, there's multiple...
Oh, right.
Okay.
Dead Duff?
Give me that flight.
I'm gonna go do the other boss then.
Aw, shit!
We're cooked!
It is officially over!
What the hell is that?
Is that an eye?
I think there's an eye somewhere.
What the...
Holy crap!
What the hell is that?
Oh no, it's dark now.
What the hell?
Wow, did I just get two-shotted there?
Like, I had two hearts and I just got hit once and I lost both?
Damn.
That was a good run though.
Solid.
Just a little unlucky that we got Delirium so fast.
At the end, like, I could have done with some more other bosses first, right?
Decent run though.
We did some unlocks.
Yep, yep.
I would say, all in all, success.
For sure.
What's up, guys?
Did you enjoy yourselves?
I think I did pretty well today.
We got a bunch of unlocks.
Like, ten unlocks or something in total.
Maybe eight.
Oh, I forgot about Magician, you're right.
True.
I don't think it would have helped me.
I was cooked no matter what.
Like, I had four HP when I came in there.
There is no way in hell I would have done all that.
Yeah, Minecraft Season 3, July 17.
On Twitch.
At...
3 o'clock.
Same start as this stream.
Yeah.
I'm looking forward to that.
The only problem with that is, guys, it's probably gonna be a bunch of...
Uh, what do you call it?
Fever...
Fever Dream Streams.
Because the temperature in July is gonna be insane.
Unless...
The AC that I ordered...
Is actually gonna be operational at that time.
Maybe.
We'll see.
Really curious about the new game this week?
Yeah, I haven't started it yet.
But I have a couple games in mind that I'm gonna play.
Uh, maybe tomorrow or the day after I'm gonna start it.
I don't wanna say what it is yet, cause I don't wanna get your hopes up in case I change my mind, right?
But yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
It's gonna be a good one.
Unfortunate...
Dude, I was gonna play Red Dead Redemption 2.
I was so incredibly hyped for that.
After the first Red Dead Redemption.
But I had audio issues that I just couldn't fix.
And people in the community even tried to help me out with it.
And I tried all kinds of things.
I couldn't get it to work, man.
So, the plan is...
We're gonna wait for...
Either...
Sometime in the future when I have different PC components that will, you know, by pure chance...
Allow me to play the game without audio issues.
Or, Rockstar releases a 60 FPS patch for the console.
If that happens, then I'll play it on console.
Even though I really would love to play it with mouse and keyboard.
That's why I'm so insistent on trying to play it on PC, you know?
You always have the weirdest issues with the game, but this is like an issue that everyone has.
I don't understand how nobody is saying anything about it.
Like, it's an insane problem.
I literally can't play it.
It hurts my ear.
That was an audio problem where it would do like a pop or like a crackle and a pop in the ears whenever something happens in game.
Like, I don't want to say exactly what it was, but many different things contributed to that.
Yeah.
I got it on Rockstar Launcher.
But guys, I tried everything.
Like, even sailing the seven seas.
Just to see if it has something to do with that.
Didn't work.
Same thing.
I tried things, okay?
OBS-ish?
No, no, no, it's an in-game thing.
Like, even with OBS not even running, because all my testing was done without even recording.
So, the first time I launched it, obviously I was recording it.
And, as soon as this stuff started happening, I was like, Okay, we got some issues here, but maybe it'll go away.
And it just kept happening.
And then there was crackle as well.
And it just kept ruining things.
So I was like, guys, I gotta stop the recording here and try to figure it out and I'll be back.
That's what I said in the recording, you know?
And I guess I never came back because I couldn't fix it.
No, I got it from some other website, geezmo.
What sort of rations?
I don't know, uh...
I don't know, but I will say, on the trip there, there were definitely some, uh...
Some torrential rains.
And it was hard to not capsize.
That never came home, yeah, exactly.
But I'm glad I didn't upload anything, because imagine I uploaded the first episode of Red Dead 2.
And then, you know...
I mean, it would have been 20 minutes long, so it didn't even make sense.
Yeah.
It's so annoying that I had that problem.
It really pisses- pisses me off.
Because I- I was so incredibly hyped to play it.
Especially because of the end of Red Dead 1, you know?
I was so incredibly excited about it and all that.
Such a letdown.
Okay, you got me, Estrogeny.
I was- I was playing Minecraft.
I- I'm sorry.
It was- it was all a lie!
I was just sitting there playing Minecraft.
Yeah, tech issues honestly are the worst.
And I really miss TotalBiscuit.
Do you guys know who TotalBiscuit was?
He's like one of the few people that would review a game and put emphasis on the performance of the game.
He's the only guy I could trust when it came to that stuff.
Because I'd see all these other reviewers, you know, review a game and be like, Yeah, performance is pretty good.
Then I install it.
Runs like shit.
Bugs up the wazoo.
You know?
Totally immersion breaking.
I miss TotalBiscuit, man.
Yeah.
Because we had the same mindset when it comes to what a consumer should expect from a video game, you know?
And honestly, I think performance is up there among the most important things you can have in a video game.
If the performance isn't there, I almost don't want to play it, no matter what.
Even if it's the best game in the world.
I just don't want to.
It's completely immersion breaking.
I mean, Pochismo, if you have some suggestions, I am more than willing to try it.
Just know that I've tried so many things already with Red Dead 2, that I don't think you can surprise me with a new idea.
The next big thing I could try is to install Linux and run it via that.
But even then, I've seen people complain about the same issue running on Linux.
So I don't know, man.
It sounds bad, you know?
The thing is though, I don't care too much if it's like 30 FPS.
As long as it's consistent 30 FPS, you know what I mean?
But yeah, I mean, in terms of Red Dead 2, obviously you want to play it in 4K and...
Now that we live in 2026, you know, you want to play it in...
60 FPS, if not even more, 120 in my case, right?
On a 4K screen with mouse and keyboard.
Would be a damn shame to capitulate and play it on an old version of the game from 2018, I guess it was.
That doesn't run very well, you know?
It's just... I don't know, man.
I tried looking into community mods as well, G-Game, and believe you me, I even tried modding the game myself.
I tried it.
Fucking Opus 4.8, Ultra Code.
I tried with the hardest weaponry I had.
Unfortunately, we don't have access to those files.
It's something in the engine.
It's not something we have access to.
There's a popping sound and crackle when there's, like, ambient sounds playing.
But it's totally random.
This is the really annoying part.
There were so many times when...
When I thought I had fixed it, you know?
Because I didn't hear anything for, like, two minutes.
I was like, holy shit, I did it!
Nice!
And then it came back.
So it's totally not reproducible, except it is in my case because it's, like, constant, you know?
Yeah.
But it's, like, so annoying to try and fix.
But you can look on Discord if you want to see what I've tried, if you want to suggest something I can try.
Because I still have the game installed.
I'm willing to try whatever, guys.
Because I want to play it.
If not now, at least in the future.
Look inside the Red Dead 2 discussion on Discord.
There's a pinned message in there.
Yeah, there's a pinned message of what I've tried.
And what other people have suggested that I try.
And I've been looking through that, you know?
And trying everything.
And so far, none of it has worked.
I even put in all my system specs.
So you know what I'm dealing with.
I'm on Windows 11.
Uh, everything is there for you to know.
Yeah.
Uh, how will I decide which mods to run?
I don't know yet.
I'm still thinking about it.
So I can't really answer that question yet.
My guess is, I'm probably just gonna decide on something really simple.
You know, and install it.
I don't want to overcomplicate it too much.
I don't think I'm gonna do a mod pack or something like that.
I'm just gonna install one big mod.
Like create, right?
But I heard people say that there's also an add-on to create with some flying stuff.
So maybe I'll do both of those if I do create.
So...
I would probably do that and then nothing else on top of that, you know?
That's what I would suspect.
But I could change my mind.
I'm gonna do some research on it in the not-too-distant future.
And maybe my research will make me change my mind.
I don't know.
I mean, obviously I'll get mods like sodium and all those performance stuff, right?
Strong mod opinions.
Oh yeah, those two are a good bet.
Nice.
No unless here.
It's gonna end up with everybody saying, no, no, no, you should do this.
No, no, no, you should do that, you know?
I mean, Mr. Tanooki, why- What is the point of installing the prism launcher?
Is the normal launcher not good enough?
Is it gonna change anything for me?
Oh, what's up, Dr. B?
It went amazing.
Got a bunch of unlocks today.
Yeah, all in all, I would say, uh, success.
Successful progress.
Good proc.
As the kids say.
And they do say that.
I've noticed.
It's faster, easier, and you can install mods directly into it.
Okay, maybe I'll do that then.
But that's the thing, I'll figure that out, you know?
I'll sit down one afternoon with a cup of coffee, and I'll Google...
Minecraft...
mods.
What do you suggest?
You know, and I'm gonna look through.
I'm gonna see what's out there.
Do my own research.
Yeah, what is it with all the sex mods?
I know there's, like, sex mods for...
Skyrim and...
Fallout.
It's always Bethesda games for some reason.
And other games like that, like...
I don't understand...
The obsession with that, when you have access to something like Pornhub.
Why?
Maybe it's just old-fashioned?
It's weird, man.
Yeah, I...
I don't know, man.
Yeah, okay.
Fine.
Oliver Jenny...
What is Jenny mod?
I don't know what that is.
Unless you're referring to...
The cat I had in Minecraft called Jenny.
Wasn't there a cat called Jenny?
Or am I misremembering that?
I'm pretty sure there was a cat called Jenny.
And maybe Jenny died.
Oh, Jenny is one of those mods?
I see.
Okay.
Hey.
Quick question.
If I were to install Jenny mod...
Is that actually against Twitch TOS?
Are people playing that on Twitch?
Okay.
But it would...
Because it would be kind of funny...
To be like...
Okay, guys.
We're doing modded playthrough, you know?
And then have Jenny mod installed.
And be like...
Here we go!
I'm playing it blind!
Let's see if we can get her panties off!
I don't know what the mod is about.
But I'm just assuming here, you know?
Dude, that would be hilarious.
But yeah, I would get banned so fast.
That's horrible.
Install a fake Jenny mod triggers?
But how would I even do that without knowing something about it, right?
I would have to have intricate knowledge of it.
Unless I just ask Claude or something.
I haven't been following anything with Deltarune, guys.
I will play Deltarune when it's done.
I don't know when that happens, but...
At some point in the future, right?
It's like a TV show.
I don't wanna watch one series or...
One season and then wait years for the next.
Even though sometimes I fall into that trap.
Like, I watched Pluribus Season 1.
And I regret doing it, because I want more.
So I'll just have to watch the first season again, I guess.
When the rest comes out.
Okay, guys, I gotta go!
Jackie is rubbing up against my leg like crazy, because she wants to eat.
Even though she still has food, so I don't know what's wrong with her.
I'm gonna feed her, and I'm gonna feed myself.
Thanks for showing up to this.
It's good to be back.
We had a successful proc today.
And we're gonna have more streams.
And...
This week, new game.
Coming soon.
To your TV.
Bye-bye.